Guy Lamdan

ISR AEL · guylamdan00@gmail.com

PROFILE

Experienced customer service and sales manager with high technical skills.

Dedicated to providing solutions and maintaining good communication with customers in a fast-paced highly technical environment.

Proven ability to establish great workflow in a limited schedule.

Highly motivated, hard-working, team player.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Assistant Manager, Bike Way Jerusalem

Sep 2020 — Present, Jerusalem

- I am in charge of sales, inventory, and store workflow managing.
- I provide solutions to customers and employees using my knowledge and experience from many years of working in the field.
- Headed the store's upgrade into computerized ERP and inventory management.
- Inserted a workflow system to improve the store's repair workshop efficiency.

Bicycle Mechanic, La-Medavesh bike store

Jan 2016 — Sep 2020, Kibutz Be'eri

- Between the years 2017-2020 I managed the store's repair workshop.
- I was in charge of providing technical solutions for a wide range of problems in customers' bicycles using the knowledge I acquired working as the secondary mechanic in the store.
- Managed the workshop's customer relations and made sure to provide any of the customers' needs.
- · Managed the workshop's inventory and workflow.

EDUCATION

Sha'ar Ha-Negev regional school, Graduate

Sep 2003 — Jun 2015, Sha'ar Ha-Negev District

During my high school years I was a cadet pro cyclist.

- 2011 Israel XCM mountain bike national champion, ages 13-14.
- 2011 Israel XCO mountain bike Vice-champion, ages 13-14.
- 2013 Israel road racing national champion, ages 15-16.
- 2013 Israel national road cycling team member, ages 15-16.
- 2013 2nd place at the West-Spain track cycling championship.
- 2014 I was accepted to Wingate Academy of sports.

COURSES

Unreal Engine C++ Development, Udemy

May 2020 — May 2021

REFERENCES

References available upon request

DETAILS

Israel

0546325909

DATE OF BIRTH

03.06.1997

LANGUAGES

Hebrew Native speaker
English Native speaker

HOBBIES

Playing guitar. Stock trading. Playing tennis.